Kyle Owen Ga

gakyleowen@gmail.com (+63) 939-119-2839 DECA HOMES Cabantian Davao City, Davao Region

Summary

An ambitious software engineer with three years of professional experience, including serving as Developer Lead at https://discrete.nih.gov/html/ engineer with three years of professional experience, including serving as Developer Lead at https://discrete.nih.gov/html/ engineer with three years of professional experience, including serving as Developer Lead at https://discrete.nih.gov/html/ engineer with three years of professional experience, including serving as Developer Lead at https://discrete.nih.gov/html/ engineer with three years of professional experience, including serving as Developer Lead at https://discrete.nih.gov/html/ engineer with three years of professional experience, including serving as Developer Lead at https://discrete.nih.gov/html/ engineer with a proven ability to adapt to new technologies, paired with strong communication and team management skills that drive collaboration and project success. Explore my portfolio https://discrete.nih.gov/html/ engineer with a proven ability to adapt to new technologies, paired with strong communication and team management skills that drive collaboration and project success. Explore my portfolio https://discrete.nih.gov/html/ engineer with a proven ability to adapt to new technologies, paired with strong communication and team management skills that drive collaboration and project success. Explore my portfolio https://discrete.nih.gov/html/ engineer with a proven ability to adapt to new technologies, paired with strong communication and team management skills that drive collaboration and project success.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

AMA Computer College • Davao City, Davao Region 2019–2022 **Dean's Lister**

08/2022

Skills

Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, C#, Python

Backend Frameworks: ExpressJS (GraphQL and REST API), Laravel, ASP.NET Web API

Databases: PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Frontend Frameworks & Libraries: React, React Native, Next.js, Vue, Ant Design, Chakra UI, Tailwind, Bootstrap

Experience

Developer Lead

Hill&Foster - Calgary AB, Canada (Full-time, Remote)

05/2022 -11/2024

- Lead the implementation for the designs making it responsive and dynamic base on branding.
- Worked on various clients projects such as corporate websites, e-Commerce site, and custom web development.
- Developed full-stack applications using popular JavaScript frameworks (React js, Next js, React Native) on the front-end and .NET Framework for the back-end.

Developer II

Fire Safety Inspection Certification System of Bureau of Fire Protection (Davao City)

02/2022 - 05/2022

. Built the front-end for the Certification System for Applicants and Bureau of Fire Protection Employees.

Developer II

FWD Springboard Student Challenge • Davao City, Davao Region

09/2021 - 11/2021

- · Won Top 3 in the National Level
- · Developed a social media mobile application (with React Native) that allows easy access to insurance